Space. It's not as deep as you think.
Muppets from Space is a family, comedy, science
fiction film directed by Tim Hill.
When Gonzo's breakfast cereal tells him that he's the descendant of aliens from another planet, his attempts at extraterrestrial
communication get him kidnapped by a secret government agency, prompting the Muppets to spring into action to rescue their friend.
Gonzo / Dr. Bunsen Honeydew / Waldorf / The
Birdman (voice), played by Dave Goelz.
Kermit the Frog / Rizzo the Rat / Beaker / Cosmic Fish #1 / Rainbow /
Miss Piggy (assistant) (voice), played by Steve Whitmire.
Pepe the Prawn / Bobo as Rentro / Johnny Fiama / Bubba the Rat /
Cosmic Fish #2 (voice), played by Bill Barretta.
Robin / Statler / Ubergonzo (voice), played by Jerry Nelson.
Dr. Phil Van Neuter / Sal Minella (voice), played by Brian Henson.
Clifford (voice), played by Kevin Clash.
Muppets from Space is a 1999 American science fiction comedy film directed by Tim Hill in his
directorial debut and written by Jerry Juhl, Joseph Mazzarino, and Ken Kaufman.
It is the sixth theatrical film featuring the Muppets.
The film stars Muppet performers Steve Whitmire, Dave Goelz, Jerry Nelson,
Bill Barretta, and Frank Oz, as well as Jeffrey Tambor, F.
Murray Abraham, David Arquette, Josh Charles, Hollywood Hogan in his final feature
film appearance, Ray Liotta, Rob Schneider and Andie MacDowell.
In the film, Gonzo attempts to discover his origins.
After he and Rizzo the Rat are captured by government officials during his search,
Kermit the Frog and the rest of the Muppets set out to rescue them.
The film was produced by Columbia Pictures and Jim Henson Pictures and
released on July 14, 1999 by Sony Pictures Releasing.
It grossed $22.3 million against a budget of $24 million
and received mixed reviews from critics.
It is the last Muppet film to involve Oz and Juhl, the last theatrically released Muppet film to be produced by the Jim Henson Company before
the franchise was acquired by the Walt Disney Company in 2004, and the last theatrically released film until The Muppets in 2011.
The film explores themes of alien, puppetry, anthropomorphic puppets, muppets.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.